Greg Duke

22 Westgate Burnley BB11 1RT

07521669230

gregduke92@gmail.com

https://github.com/SatsumaSegment

Profile

I'm a highly motivated and hard-working individual, with a keen interest in computers, electronics and anything technology related. I have over eight years' experience assembling and repairing PC and laptop hardware.

I have developed a number of software applications as a self-taught programmer and enjoy tinkering with microcontrollers such as the Arduino, Raspberry Pi and ESP-32.

I have knowledge in several programming languages including C, C++, Python and Javascript, as well as style languages, such as HTML, CSS and Kivy.

I have recently completed Harvard's CS50x: Introduction to Computer Science course, achieving 100% grade across all assignments.

Skills

- Critical thinking
- Problem solving
- Meeting deadlines

- Organised
- Quick learner
- Attention to detail

Work Experience

Jun 2018 - Present

PC Builds and Repairs, Self-employed

- Building and repairing desktop and laptop computers
- Tailoring PCs to users' individual needs
- Cleaning components
- Tuning computers
- Detecting and removing malicious software

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Solderer, Orisec LTD

- Soldering components to circuit boards as per circuit diagrams
- Surface-mount soldering
- De-soldering components, including surface-mount, for repairs

• Operating flow solder machine

Jan 2014 - Mar 2018

Production Operative, Novatech

- Picking components
- Building PCs adherent to specification sheets
- Testing PCs for quality assurance
- Configuring BIOS
- Configuring RAID systems
- Overclocking
- Packaging and labelling PCs for shipping

Education and Qualifications

2022

Introduction to Computer Science, Harvard-X Verified Certificate of Completion (100%)

Skills developed: understanding of the fundamental processes involved in computing, abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, cybersecurity and resource management; knowledge of multiple coding languages and style conventions; ability to think computationally.

2009 - 2011 Animal Management, South Downs College

BTEC Level 3

NCFE Level 2 in Employability Skills

2008 - 2009 IT, St Vincent's College

BTEC Level 2

Functional Skills in English (GCSE equivalent)

Skills developed: proficiency in MS Office; website development; customising applications software; database and spreadsheet software; ICT graphics.

2003 - 2008 St Edmund's Secondary School

4 GCSEs A - C

Including: Maths and Science

City & Guilds in Building Craft Occupations